Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
Koby was held at the Pirate Island
of Beehive by Blackbeard.
Hey!
I'll help you out,
so free Moria-sama who is being held
in a cell further in from here!
Koby managed to escape and tried to free
other prisoners by becoming a decoy.
While the island was thrown into turmoil,
other marine soldiers
appeared at the port.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
She's whipping a building...
Why are you staring at me?
I'll discipline you.
Everyone's in place!
We'll be ready soon!
JUSTICE
"For the Beloved Pupil -
The Fist of Vice Admiral Garp!"
This is...
too many...
Plus, this shackle...
Isn't there any way to survive?
This is it, Koby the hero!
I'll be taking that bounty!
Fire!
What?!
What?
What? What?
What?!
It's beautiful!
Wait, no! What the hell is this?!
Why did a flower come out of the muzzle?!
No, wait...
This is...
something that Dr. Vegapunk invented...
which earned him the Mobel Peace Prize!
That's not what I'm asking!
Who did this?!
Koby-senpai!
Get over here!
Wait, no!
I didn't mean anythin' weird!
HIBARI, MARINE HQ COMMANDER (SWORD)
Hibari-san! Why are you here?!
Don't tell me...
That's right! I shot Flower Bullets,
the flowers that bloom out of gunpowder!
The enemies can't use their weapons!
Get away quickly while you can!
A-And...
if you're hungry, I...
made...
bento for you!
What?
No, I mean...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Prince! Any progress?
Yeah, our task has just been completed.
PRINCE GRUS,
MARINE HQ REAR ADMIRAL (SWORD)
Koby is okay, too!
GLORP-GLORP FRUIT, CLAY-MAN
MUD PUPPET (GOLEM)
My mud puppets
are not so easy to take down.
I'll keep them busy fighting out there.
The pirates can't get
anywhere near the open area.
What are these bastards?!
And...
JUSTICE
...they can't escape from there, either!
H-Hey... Has this open area
always been shaped like this?
What?
Isn't that building moving?
H-Hey, wait!
Oh, no... we can't get out of here!
See, you can do it if you try.
Now, whenever you're ready!
I was able to contact Prince!
It's all ready!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Come to the dead center!
Everyone, hang onto something!
Charge!
C'mon! Hurry up!
You came to rescue me, didn't you?
What?
Y-Yes! Of course!
Thank you!
What? D-Don't be...
Okay! Let's get out of here!
Look up!
What?!
A marine ship is flying up there!
Why?! How's that possible?!
Who's on it?!
Isn't it... falling towards us?
R-Run!
Look! On the ship!
No way! I thought he retired!
The legendary... hero!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Koby! I'm here to save you!
Run! Just run!
We can't... There's no way out!
Hey, you damn pirates!
He's coming! Run!
Vice Admiral Garp...
Why?! I'm not worthy enough to save...
You fools!
Who do you think you have kidnapped?!
Koby is the future of the marines!
And...
he's also my beloved pupil!
Galaxy...
Impact!
If we don't run, it'll crash into us!
Why did he come to Beehive?!
Cumulo-glorpus!
He destroyed the town with a single blow...
He still does that crazy stuff.
Damn Garp! He's insane!
I'll make that geezer pay!
Don't move, you pirates!
Just obey us!
Resistance will result in further damage!
Put your weapons down!
I'm not satisfied...
I'm off my game.
Screw you!
What's that I-could-do-better attitude
after causing this much destruction?!
We can't take any more damage!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Oh, Koby!
You're okay!
Koby, that fool...
I'm so relieved! He didn't get killed!
Koby-kun, I'm glad that you're okay.
Good work, everyone.
Gee... He overdid it.
Garp is a bad boy!
Garp-san said Koby's the future
of the marines. It's unforgivable!
I'll drag him down!
You've got to do those things in secret.
You spoiled brat!
So cute.
Hey!
Koby!
Captain Koby!
Everyone!
Koby-kun!
Come on! Let's go home!
Helmeppo-san! Tashigi-san!
Even those who are not SWORD members...
Everyone likes you, Koby-senpai!
Why are you carrying that, Koby?
Looks like it's hard to run with it.
Vice Admiral Garp!
We can't get the shackle removed...
And we didn't know what to do!
Please...
do...
some...
thin'...
Hibari!
Hibari-san!
You fools...
What do you think you have done?
Kuzan.
Kuzan-san!
What are you doing?! Thaw out Hibari-san!
He's Aokiji!
Captain Kuzan!
Kuzan-chan!
Kuzan-san! I'm begging you!
It's no use.
Don't get me into trouble, Koby.
I can't have you running off...
while Teach is away.
Two years ago,
over the position of the Marine
Headquarters' next Admiral of the Fleet,
a big fight erupted
between Admiral Akainu...
and Admiral Aokiji.
After 10 days of a deadly struggle,
the victory went to...
Akainu.
Akainu didn't kill Aokiji out of mercy.
However,
Aokiji refused to serve under Akainu.
And he left the marines.
SOME ISLAND, NEW WORLD
What the...
Blackbeard's here!
Run! Get out of the town!
Hey!
What happened here?
Wait! Who did this?!
No, I don't need to ask...
There is only one person in the world
who can do this!
It's you!
Aokiji!
My crew is frozen solid outside! Undo it!
You're annoying me.
You better not use
your Tremor-Tremor Fruit power.
They'll shatter and die.
You're their captain, so I think you know.
Do you think I started it?
And you also know what happened to me,
don't you?
I'm broken-hearted and angry.
So imagine whose fault it actually is.
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one! Helmeppo!
He is a lieutenant commander and a member
of SWORD, a top secret special force!
He was born on July 16th
and likes caviar and luxurious steak!
He is the son of a former marine
branch captain, Axe-Hand Morgan...
who was the reigning tyrant of
Shells Town.
He used to boss people around
using his father's influence.
One day,
he had Zoro arrested unreasonably.
He promised Zoro that he'd free him
if he could survive without food or drink
for a month, but he broke
his word and tried to execute Zoro.
Then he and his father got beaten
by the angry Luffy and Zoro.
He joined the marines and spent his days
doing odd jobs with Koby.
Seems like he mended his ways.
He is now flourishing
as a lieutenant commander.
When Koby was kidnapped by Blackbeard,
Helmeppo raised his voice
to take him back.
I'm begging you guys!
We're comrades!
We alone can't possibly save him!
Helmeppo is shining brighter now
than he used to.
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
Kuzan stands in the way of Garp
who came to save Koby.
What is his true intention
in joining Blackbeard's crew
after leaving the marines?
Garp's former best pupil,
who became a pirate,
now unleashes a blow of rebellion
against his mentor!
On the next episode of ONE PIECE!
"The Marines Surprised! The Marine
Headquarters' Former Admiral, Kuzan"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm